<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Game Setup on Fullspeed Resources</title><link>https://fsfam.club/resources/game-setup/</link><description>Recent content in Game Setup on Fullspeed Resources</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 11:14:33 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fsfam.club/resources/game-setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Input Device</title><link>https://fsfam.club/resources/game-setup/input-device/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 11:15:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://fsfam.club/resources/game-setup/input-device/</guid><description>The most common input devices used in Fullspeed are keyboard and gamepad/controller. What you use typically does not matter. There are top players that use both keyboard and gamepad, who are all very consistent and can drive very fast times.
When chosing an input device for fullspeed, you should go with the one you feel the most comfortable with.
While the differences between keyboard and gamepad are neglectible in practice, there are a few differences that are worth knowing about.</description></item><item><title>Graphics</title><link>https://fsfam.club/resources/game-setup/graphics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 11:22:45 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://fsfam.club/resources/game-setup/graphics/</guid><description>Since Fullspeed is such a high-speed and intensive style to play, having good frame rate will be quite important as it helps with reaction times and seeing what is coming at you in the track.
Under Settings -&amp;gt; Graphics you will find all settings related to the graphics of the game.
Shader Quality One of the most impactful options on your FPS is the &amp;ldquo;Shader quality&amp;rdquo; option. Setting this to low, should boost your FPS by quite a bit.</description></item><item><title>Player Camera</title><link>https://fsfam.club/resources/game-setup/player-camera/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 11:22:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://fsfam.club/resources/game-setup/player-camera/</guid><description>The two main cameras people play with in Fullspeed is either Camera 1 (Overview Camera) or Camera 2 (Follow Camera).
Camera 1 sits a bit higher and gives sort of an overview of the car. It lags a bit behind the directional vector of your car which makes it a very useful camera for jumps and some other styles like ICE where you drive sideways. Many use this camera in fullspeed as it gives a more consistent overview.</description></item><item><title>Custom Skid Marks</title><link>https://fsfam.club/resources/game-setup/custom-skid-marks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 11:22:56 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://fsfam.club/resources/game-setup/custom-skid-marks/</guid><description>TrackMania allows you to override certain textures in the game by creating some folders that the game actively looks for. With this feature, it is possible to change the look and texture of your skid marks. This is helpful in Fullspeed as we can increase the visiblity of our skid marks.
snixtho discovered the technique to do this for asphalt, and you can read more about how to change your skid marks or even make your own here.</description></item><item><title>Openplanet</title><link>https://fsfam.club/resources/game-setup/openplanet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 11:23:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://fsfam.club/resources/game-setup/openplanet/</guid><description>Openplanet is an extension platform developed by Miss. It allows you to download plugins and add extra functionality to the base game. There are alot of useful tools that can improve your game experience.
For more information about downloading and installing Openplanet, check out the website at openplanet.dev.
Recommended Plugins Here is a list of plugins that we can recommend Fullspeed players and to improve your game experience in general.</description></item></channel></rss>